✔ S7 current exact occurrence resolves a different catalog without selection mutation (2.7835ms)
✔ S7 generic unavailable replaced (0.2363ms)
✔ S7 generic unavailable released (0.1842ms)
✔ S7 generic unavailable withdrawn (0.1543ms)
✔ S7 generic unavailable cycle changed (0.1507ms)
✔ S7 generic unavailable closed (0.1183ms)
✔ S7 generic unavailable deleted (0.0925ms)
✔ S7 generic unavailable missing (0.0908ms)
✔ S7 generic unavailable denied (0.1477ms)
✔ S7 generic unavailable forged actor (0.1414ms)
✔ S7 generic unavailable stale revision (0.1538ms)
✔ S7 current and stale friendship FRIEND_REQUEST (0.1772ms)
✔ S7 current and stale friendship FRIEND_ACCEPTED (0.0502ms)
✔ S7 legacy Activity never becomes versioned after technical upgrade (0.0648ms)
✔ S7 no private reads or active-career mutation; actor fallback retained (0.4891ms)
✔ rollout maintenance/recovery differs from strict final Rules by exactly one false literal (0.3268ms)
✔ rollout generator fails closed on missing, duplicate or already paused gate (0.4079ms)
✔ rollout artifacts are reproducible, self-contained, use exact indexes and contain no project or credentials (1.0362ms)
✔ rollout maintenance services block all four new-event actions before SDK work, never report success (2.4283ms)
✔ rollout normal services retain the four transaction entry points (2.6862ms)
✔ rollout maintenance does not locally disable rejection, membership, cleanup, rename or close (1.1637ms)
✔ rollout maintenance notice is accessible, explicit and absent from normal UI (1.6824ms)
✔ rollout Friends UI disables send/accept only, preserves reject and search (2.1125ms)
✔ rollout JointPlan UI disables creation/invitation while preserving existing-plan operations (5.1212ms)
✔ rollout build flag is explicit, validated, build-only and independent from Emulator isolation (0.4985ms)
✔ activity repository owns two bounded queries and adapts timestamps (0.8491ms)
✔ activity repository normalizes, orders, drops invalid data and stops callbacks (1.0232ms)
✔ activity repository cache and pending writes are loading, not empty ready (0.3525ms)
✔ activity repository rejects wrong uid and replacement session including same uid (0.4236ms)
✔ activity mark read marked (0.4608ms)
✔ activity mark read already (0.2823ms)
✔ activity mark read missing (0.265ms)
✔ activity mark read reinvited (0.2751ms)
✔ activity mark read aborts session replacement during read and rejects invalid document (0.5253ms)
✔ activity transaction retry rechecks replacement slot (0.3176ms)
✔ activity denied stale write reconciles read-only but never hides a live permission failure (92.8751ms)
✔ activity session shares listeners across consumers and repeated same-user updates (0.6718ms)
✔ activity session A to B, logout and same uid new session reject late callbacks (0.2777ms)
✔ activity session errors are independent and retry replaces subscriptions (0.1366ms)
✔ activity session unknown badge on corruption, cap and local horizon expiry without new listeners (0.1796ms)
✔ activity session asynchronous mark completion cannot cross session boundary (0.3465ms)
✔ activity session clock skew does not claim an exact badge from a truncated future window (0.0838ms)
✔ activity presentation FRIEND_REQUEST_RECEIVED (0.0801ms)
✔ activity presentation FRIEND_REQUEST_ACCEPTED (0.0264ms)
✔ activity presentation JOINT_PLAN_INVITATION (0.0198ms)
✔ activity relative time preserves ISO and uses short local dates (11.0509ms)
✔ activity bell badge null (1.9395ms)
✔ activity bell badge {"count":0,"isCapped":false} (0.7682ms)
✔ activity bell badge {"count":3,"isCapped":false} (0.6997ms)
✔ activity bell badge {"count":50,"isCapped":false} (0.6699ms)
✔ activity bell badge {"count":50,"isCapped":true} (0.6395ms)
✔ activity popover opens without reads, focuses, Escape/outside/toggle close and cleanup (0.9654ms)
✔ activity panel loading and retry (0.7321ms)
✔ activity panel ready and retry (0.736ms)
✔ activity panel error and retry (0.7137ms)
✔ activity item read state, native action, time and independent actor fallback (1.0421ms)
✔ activity activation marked (0.273ms)
✔ activity activation alreadyRead (0.0628ms)
✔ activity activation stale (0.0458ms)
✔ activity activation missing (0.0337ms)
✔ activity activation error (0.0344ms)
✔ activity activation cancelled (0.0311ms)
✔ activity friendship navigates safely on success/error and timeout has no plan selection (2.122ms)
✔ activity joint target uses authorized current-career plans only (0.1245ms)
✔ activity shell hook owns one session, deduplicates actors and isolates auth replacement (1.5563ms)
✔ activity panel item uses exact instance and navigates without writing on open (1.2026ms)
✔ activity Planner intention waits for authorized list and consumes once without selecting hidden plans (1.842ms)
✔ activity panel interaction stale stays safe (1.5535ms)
✔ activity panel interaction missing stays safe (1.17ms)
✔ activity panel interaction error stays safe (0.9075ms)
✔ activity profiles have a fallback without blocking list or retrying failed actor per render (0.9349ms)
✔ activity read label retains accessible text with its own globally applicable clipped class (1.5222ms)
✔ D2 T1 request retains C1 (0.258ms)
✔ D2 T2 accepted retains C1 (0.2076ms)
✔ D2 T3 C1/C2 distinct identities (0.0766ms)
✔ D2 T4 ID/payload cycle mismatch rejected (0.0734ms)
✔ D2 T5 missing/malformed cycle rejected (0.1615ms)
✔ D2 T6 invitation retains exact occurrence wire contract (0.1604ms)
✔ D2 T7 old/new occurrences distinct, old readAt independent (0.0924ms)
✔ D2 T8 plan alone cannot identify new occurrence (0.0738ms)
✔ D2 T9 decoder supplies no authorization or state inference (0.0833ms)
✔ D2 T10 extra academic/access claims rejected (0.0615ms)
✔ D2 T11 inputs not mutated or aliased on read (0.0568ms)
✔ D2 T12 legacy v1 continues through opt-in decoder (0.1649ms)
✔ D2 read decoder requires resolved timestamps, builders preserve adapter sentinel (0.0672ms)
✔ activity deterministic schema: FRIEND_REQUEST_RECEIVED (0.1927ms)
✔ activity deterministic schema: FRIEND_REQUEST_ACCEPTED (0.0606ms)
✔ activity deterministic schema: JOINT_PLAN_INVITATION (0.0471ms)
✔ activity rejects unknown type, path injection and invalid target grammar (0.1383ms)
✔ activity normalizes resolved FRIEND_REQUEST_RECEIVED (0.2065ms)
✔ activity normalizes resolved FRIEND_REQUEST_ACCEPTED (0.0783ms)
✔ activity normalizes resolved JOINT_PLAN_INVITATION (0.0478ms)
✔ activity normalization rejects schema safely (0.0992ms)
✔ activity normalization rejects type safely (0.0545ms)
✔ activity normalization rejects extra safely (0.0345ms)
✔ activity normalization rejects actor empty safely (0.0433ms)
✔ activity normalization rejects actor whitespace safely (0.0386ms)
✔ activity normalization rejects actor primitive safely (0.0452ms)
✔ activity normalization rejects target kind safely (0.0565ms)
✔ activity normalization rejects target empty safely (0.0493ms)
✔ activity normalization rejects target extra safely (0.0487ms)
✔ activity normalization rejects created missing safely (0.0518ms)
✔ activity normalization rejects created sentinel safely (0.0392ms)
✔ activity normalization rejects created string safely (0.0351ms)
✔ activity normalization rejects read malformed safely (0.0502ms)
✔ activity rejects each missing field and mismatched slot (0.1881ms)
✔ activity timestamp boundary preserves nanoseconds and rejects ambiguous values (0.1443ms)
✔ activity read state includes readAt equal to createdAt (0.0945ms)
✔ activity reinvitation distinguishes nanosecond instances without changing slot (0.0837ms)
✔ activity sorting uses precise DESC and ordinal slot ASC on ties (0.1507ms)
✔ activity filters are closed and badge represents zero, exact cap and overflow (0.2461ms)
✔ activity horizon includes exact 90 days and now, excludes older and future nanos (0.186ms)
✔ activity normalization detaches immutable inputs and tolerates corrupt neighbors (0.2693ms)
✔ subject picker preserves unknown people in all/subset grouping and searches names or codes (1.1431ms)
✔ review distinguishes invitations, departed people and missing academic information (0.8125ms)
✔ shared add dialog reviews first, prevents loading overwrites and saves only on explicit confirmation (3.0764ms)
✔ plan academic context never reads a nonfriend and releases listeners when its context changes (1.1933ms)
✔ multi hook clears a removed friend immediately and ignores late snapshot/profile callbacks (1.2447ms)
✔ joint hook discards subjects immediately on leave and stops all listeners on signout/unmount (1.1259ms)
✔ delete progress requires explicit confirmation, focuses cancel and blocks duplicate submissions (1.056ms)
✔ App reset retains its original transform and is exposed only in the subjects panel (0.3945ms)
✔ delete plan requires confirmation, blocks duplicates and keeps the dialog open on failure (0.942ms)
✔ closed membership keeps the subjects subscription, deletion lock clears it (0.7278ms)
ℹ tests 123
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 123
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 209.1286
